brandyourself.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy | BrandYourself

Effective Date of Current Policy: April 3rd, 2019

### 1\. PURPOSE

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the BrandYourself Terms of Service (the “ **Terms** ”). The terms “BrandYourself,” “we,” and “us” include BrandYourself.com, Inc. and our affiliates and subsidiaries. This Privacy Policy explains our online and offline information practices, the kinds of information we may collect, how we intend to use and share that information, and how you can opt-out of a use or correct or change such information. All other terms not defined in Section 13 or otherwise herein will have the meanings set forth in the Terms.

### 2\. SCOPE

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information that is Processed by BrandYourself in the course of our business, including on BrandYourself websites (each a “Site”), mobile applications, forums, blogs, and other online or offline offerings (together with any and all future online and offline offerings operated by or on behalf of BrandYourself, the “Services”). All individuals whose responsibilities include the Processing of Personal Information on behalf of BrandYourself are expected to protect that data by adherence to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is intended to meet requirements globally, including those in North America, Europe, APAC, and other jurisdictions.

### 3\. TRANSPARENCY/NOTICE—TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

The types of Personal Information we may collect (directly from you or from Third-Party sources) and our privacy practices depend on the nature of the relationship you have with BrandYourself and the requirements of applicable law. Some of the ways that BrandYourself may collect Personal Information include:

  * You may provide Personal Information directly to BrandYourself through interacting with the Services, participating in surveys, during events such as sweepstakes, and requesting Services, or information.

  * As you navigate the Services, certain passive information may also be collected about your visit, including through cookies and similar technologies as described below.

We endeavor to collect only that information which is relevant for the purposes of Processing. Below are the ways we collect Personal Information and how we use it.

### 3.1 TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

BrandYourself collects Personal Information regarding its current, prospective, and former clients, customers, users, visitors, and guests (collectively “ **Individuals** ”).

  * **Information You Provide Directly to Us.** When you use the Services or engage in certain activities, such as registering for an account with BrandYourself, responding to surveys, requesting Services or information, or contacting us directly, we may ask you to provide some or all of the following types of information:

    * **Communications with Us.** We may collect Personal Information from you such as name, email address, phone number or mailing address when you contact us or request information about our Services, register for a newsletter or loyalty program, request to receive customer or technical support, and a password when you create an account. We may further collect Personal Information from you such as payment and billing information when you register for a premium Service.

    * **Surveys.** From time to time, we may contact you to participate in online surveys. If you do decide to participate, you may be asked to provide certain information which may include Personal Information. All information collected from your participation in our surveys is provided by you voluntarily. We may use such information to improve our products, Sites and/or services and in any manner consistent with the policies provided herein.

    * **Posting on the Site.** BrandYourself may offer publicly accessible pages, blogs, private messages, or community forums. You should be aware that, when you disclose information about yourself in or on BrandYourself’s pages, blogs, private messages, and community forums, the Site will collect the information you provide in such submissions, including any Personal Information. If you choose to submit content to any public area of the Site, such content will be considered “public” and will not be subject to the privacy protections set forth herein.

    * **Registration for Sweepstakes or Contests.** Occasionally, BrandYourself may run sweepstakes and contests. We ask those who enter in the sweepstakes or contests to provide contact information (e.g., an e-mail address). If you participate in a sweepstakes or contest, your contact information may be used to reach you about the sweepstakes or contest, and for other promotional, marketing and business purposes. All sweepstakes/contests entry forms will provide a way for participants to opt-out of any communications that are not related to awarding prizes.

    * **Automatic Data Collection.** We may collect certain information automatically through our Services or other methods of web analysis, such as your Internet protocol (IP) address, cookie identifiers, ISP or mobile carrier, mobile advertising identifiers, MAC address, IMEI, Advertiser ID, and other device identifiers and features that are automatically assigned to your computer or device when you access the Internet, browser type and add-ons and language, proxy server, URL, geo-location information, hardware type, operating system, Internet service provider, pages that you visit before and after using the Services, the date and time of your visit, the amount of time you spend on each page, information about the links you click and pages you view within the Services, and other actions taken through use of the Services such as preferences.

  * **Information Submitted Via Services.** You agree that BrandYourself is free to use the content of any communications submitted by you via the Services, including any ideas, inventions, concepts, techniques, or know-how disclosed therein, for any purpose including developing, manufacturing, and/or marketing goods or Services. BrandYourself will not release your name or otherwise publicize the fact that you submitted materials or other information to us unless: (a) you grant us permission to do so; (b) we first send notice to you that the materials or other information you submit to a particular part of a Service will be published or otherwise used with your name on it; or (c) we are required to do so by law.

  * **Information from Other Sources.** We may receive information about you from other sources, including through an entity that purchases Services that you have access to use, such as your employer, school, or university, or Third-Party services and organizations to supplement information provided by you. For example, if you access our Services through a Third-Party application, such as an App Store or a Social Networking Site (“SNS”) (e.g., Facebook), we may collect information about you from that Third-Party application that you have made public via your privacy settings or have otherwise allowed us access to. Information we collect through App Stores or SNS accounts may include your name, your SNS user identification number, your SNS user name, location, sex, birth date, email, profile picture, your posts or comments, images you have posted and your contacts on the SNS. This supplemental information allows us to verify information that you have provided to BrandYourself and to enhance our ability to provide you with information about our business, products, and Services.

### 3.2 HOW BRANDYOURSELF USES YOUR INFORMATION

We acquire, hold, use, and Process Personal Information about Individuals for a variety of business purposes, including: 

  * **To Provide Products, Services, or Information Requested.** BrandYourself may use information about you to fulfill requests for products, Services, or information, including information about potential or future Services, including to:

    * Generally manage Individual information and accounts;

    * Respond to questions, comments, and other requests;

    * Provide access to certain areas, functionalities, and features of BrandYourself’s Services;

    * Contact you to answer requests for customer support or technical support;

    * Allow you to register for events; or

    * Investigate, respond to and resolve complaints and Service issues (e.g., bugs).

  * **Administrative Purposes.** BrandYourself may use Personal Information about you for its administrative purposes, including to:

    * Measure interest in BrandYourself’s Services;

    * Develop new products and Services;

    * Ensure internal quality control;

    * Verify Individual identity;

    * Communicate about Individual accounts and activities on BrandYourself’s Services and systems, and, in BrandYourself’s discretion, changes to any BrandYourself policy;

    * Send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance;

    * Process payment for products or services purchased;

    * Process applications and transactions; 

    * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; or

    * Enforce our Terms.

  * **Services via Mobile Devices.** From time to time, BrandYourself may provide Services that are specifically designed to be compatible and used on mobile devices. BrandYourself will collect certain information that your mobile device sends when you use such Services, like a device identifier, user settings, location information, mobile carrier, and the operating system of your device. Mobile versions of BrandYourself’s Services may require that users log in with an account. In such cases, information about use of mobile versions of the Services may be associated with accounts. In addition, BrandYourself may enable Individuals to download an application, widget, or other tool that can be used on mobile or other computing devices. Some of these tools may store information on mobile or other devices. These tools may transmit Personal Information to BrandYourself to enable Individuals to access accounts and to enable BrandYourself to track use of these tools. Some of these tools may enable users to email reports and other information from the tool. BrandYourself may use personal or non-identifiable information transmitted to BrandYourself to enhance these tools, to develop new tools, for quality improvement and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or in other notices BrandYourself provides.

  * **Anonymous and Aggregated Information Use.** BrandYourself may use Personal Information and other information about you to create anonymized and aggregated information, such as de-identified demographic information, de-identified location information, information about the computer or device from which you access BrandYourself’s Services, or other analyses we create. Anonymized and aggregated information is used for a variety of functions, including the measurement of visitors’ interest in and use of various portions or features of the Services. Anonymized or aggregated information is not Personal Information, and BrandYourself may use such information in a number of ways, including research, internal analysis, analytics, and any other legally permissible purposes. We may share this information within BrandYourself and with Third Parties for our or their purposes in an anonymized or aggregated form that is designed to prevent anyone from identifying you.

  * **Sharing Content with Friends or Colleagues.** BrandYourself’s Services may offer various tools and functionalities. Our referral services may allow you to forward or share certain content with a friend or colleague, such as an email inviting your friend to use our Services. Email addresses that you may provide for a friend or colleague will be used to send your friend or colleague the content or link you request, but will not be collected or otherwise used by BrandYourself or any other Third Parties for any other purpose.

  * **Other Uses.** BrandYourself may use Personal Information for which we have a legitimate interest, such as direct marketing, individual or market research, anti-fraud protection, security and investigations, or any other purpose disclosed to you at the time you provide Personal Information or with your consent.

### 3.3 COOKIES, PIXEL TAGS/WEB BEACONS, ANALYTICS INFORMATION, AND INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING

We, as well as Third Parties that provide content, advertising, or other functionality on our Services, may use cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies (“ **Technologies** ”) to automatically collect information through the Services. We use Technologies that are essentially small data files placed on your computer, tablet, mobile phone, or other devices (referred to collectively as a "device") that allow us to record certain pieces of information whenever you visit or interact with our sites, services, applications, messaging, and tools, and to recognize you across devices. Our use of cookies and other similar technologies is described more fully in our Cookie Policy.

  * **Pixel Tags/Web Beacons.** A pixel tag (also known as a web beacon) is a piece of code embedded on the Site that collects information about users’ engagement on that web page. The use of a pixel allows us to record, for example, that a user has visited a particular web page or clicked on a particular advertisement.

  * **Social Media Widgets:** Our Website includes social media features such as the Facebook “Like” button and LinkedIn (that might include widgets such as the share this button or other interactive mini-programs). These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. These social media features are either hosted by a Third Party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

  * **Analytics.** We may also use Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting or other analytics platforms to collect information regarding visitor behavior and visitor demographics on some of our Services, and to develop website content. This analytics data is not tied to any Personal Information. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can opt out of Google’s collection and Processing of data generated by your use of the Services by going to http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

If you would like to opt-out of the Technologies we employ on our sites, services, applications, or tools, you may do so by blocking, deleting, or disabling them as your browser or device permits.

### 3.4 THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES, SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORMS, AND SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT KITS

The Site may contain links to other websites and other websites may reference or link to our Site or other Services. These other domains and websites are not controlled by us, and BrandYourself does not endorse or make any representations about Third-Party websites or social media platforms. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of each and every website and application with which they interact. We do not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites or applications. Visiting these other websites or applications is at your own risk.

BrandYourself’s Services may include publicly accessible blogs, community forums, or private messaging features. The Site and our other Services may also contain links and interactive features with various social media platforms (e.g., widgets). If you already use these platforms, their cookies may be set on your device when using our Site or other Services. You should be aware that Personal Information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, chat room, social media platform or otherwise online, or that you share in an open forum may be viewed and used by others without any restrictions. We are unable to control such uses of your information when interacting with a social media platform, and by using such services you assume the risk that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties for any number of purposes.

We may use Third-Party software development kits (“ **SDKs”** ) and/or application programming interfaces (“ **APIs** ”) as part of the functionality of our Services.

### 3.5 THIRD-PARTY PAYMENT PROCESSING

We may sell virtual items or merchandise through our Services. When you make purchases through the Services, we process your payments through a Third-Party application, including the Apple App Store, Google Play App Store, Amazon App Store (together with any similar applications, “ **App Stores** ”) and Social Networking Sites such as Facebook. The Third-Party application may collect certain financial information from you to process a payment on behalf of BrandYourself, including your name, email address, address and other billing information.

### 4\. ONWARD TRANSFER—BRANDYOURSELF MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

### 4.1 INFORMATION WE SHARE

We may share your information as described in this Privacy Policy (e.g., with our Third-Party service providers; to comply with legal obligations; to protect and defend our rights and property) or with your permission.

  * **We Use Vendors and Service Providers.** We may share any information we receive with vendors and service providers. The types of service providers (processors) to whom we entrust Personal Information include (but are not limited to) service providers for (i) provision of IT and related services, including for maintenance; (ii) provision of information and services you request; (iii) payment processing; (iv) customer service activities; (v) in connection with the provision of the Site; and (vi) analysis, audit, and fraud detection. BrandYourself has executed appropriate contracts with the service providers that prohibit them from using or sharing Personal Information except as necessary to perform the contracted services on our behalf or to comply with applicable legal requirements.

  * **Business Partners.** BrandYourself may share Personal Information with our business partners, and affiliates for our and our affiliates’ internal business purposes or to provide you with a product or service that you have requested. BrandYourself may also provide Personal Information to business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. In such cases, our business partner’s name will appear, along with BrandYourself. BrandYourself requires our affiliates and business partners to agree in writing to maintain the confidentiality and security of Personal Information they maintain on our behalf and not to use it for any purpose other than the purpose for which BrandYourself provided them.

  * **Displaying to Other Users.** The content you post to the Site may be displayed on the Site. Other users of the Site may be able to see some information about you, such as your name if you submit a review. We are not responsible for privacy practices of the other users who will view and use the posted information.

  * **Marketing – Interest-Based Advertising and Third Party Marketing.** Through our Services, BrandYourself may allow Third-Party advertising partners to set tracking tools (e.g., cookies) to collect information regarding your activities (e.g., your IP address, page(s) visited, time of day). These advertising partners may use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering targeted advertisements to you when you visit non-BrandYourself related websites within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “online behavioral advertising. We may allow access to other data collected by the Site to facilitate transmittal of information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your Personal Information with Third-Party advertising partners, you may opt-out of such sharing at no cost by following the instructions in Section 5 below. Please note that opting out will not remove advertising from the pages you visit; it will mean that the ads you see may not be matched to your interests.

  * **Disclosures to Protect Us or Others (e.g., as Required by Law and Similar Disclosures).** We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other account information, and content if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: (i) comply with law enforcement or national security requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) respond to your requests; (iii) protect yours’, ours’ or others’ rights, property, or safety; (iv) to enforce BrandYourself policies or contracts; (v) to collect amounts owed to BrandYourself; (vi) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation or prosecution of suspected or actual illegal activity; or (vii) if we, in good faith, believe that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable.

In addition, from time to time, server logs may be reviewed for security purposes – e.g., to detect unauthorized activity on the Services. In such cases, server log data containing IP addresses may be shared with law enforcement bodies in order that they may identify users in connection with their investigation of the unauthorized activities.

  * **Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.** If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, then your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract. In such event, BrandYourself will endeavor to direct the transferee to use Personal Information in a manner that is consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Personal Information was collected.

### 4.2 INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS

You agree that all Personal Information collected via or by BrandYourself may be transferred, Processed, and stored anywhere in the world, including but not limited to, the United States, the European Union, in the cloud, on our servers, on the servers of our affiliates or the servers of our service providers. Your Personal Information may be accessible to law enforcement or other authorities pursuant to a lawful request. By providing information to BrandYourself, you explicitly consent to the storage of your Personal Information in these locations.

### 5\. OPT-OUT (RIGHT TO OBJECT TO PROCESSING)

### 5.1 GENERAL

You have the right to object to and opt out of certain uses and disclosures of your Personal Information. Where you have consented to BrandYourself’s Processing of your Personal Information, you may withdraw that consent at any time and opt-out to further Processing by contacting BrandYourself or BrandYourself.com, Inc., 53 West James Street, Suite 401, Lancaster, PA 17603, Attn: Privacy Policy. Even if you opt-out, we may still collect and use non-Personal Information regarding your activities on our Sites and/or information from the advertisements on Third-Party websites for non-interest based advertising purposes, such as to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements.

### 5.2 EMAIL AND TELEPHONE COMMUNICATIONS

If you receive an unwanted email from us, you can use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email to opt-out of receiving future emails. We will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. Note that you will continue to receive transaction-related emails regarding products or services you have requested. We may also send you certain non-promotional communications regarding BrandYourself and our Services and you will not be able to opt out of those communications (e.g., communications regarding updates to our Terms or this Privacy Policy).

We maintain telephone “do-not-call” and “do-not-mail” lists as mandated by law. We process requests to be placed on do-not-mail, do-not-phone and do-not-contact lists within 60 days after receipt, or such shorter time as may be required by law.

### 5.3 MOBILE DEVICES

BrandYourself may occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications with updates and other notices that may be of interest to you. You may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of communications by changing the settings on your mobile device. BrandYourself may also collect location-based information if you use our mobile applications. You may opt-out of this collection by changing the settings on your mobile device.

### 5.4 “DO NOT TRACK”

Do Not Track (“ **DNT”** ) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. Please note that we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

### 5.5 COOKIES AND INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING

As noted above and in our Cookie Policy, you may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.

To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted-out on your computer browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt-out on each device. Advertisements on Third-Party websites that contain the AdChoices link and that link to this Privacy Policy may have been directed to you based on anonymous, non-Personal Information collected by advertising partners over time and across websites. These advertisements provide a mechanism to opt-out of the advertising partners’ use of this information for interest-based advertising purposes.

### 6\. RIGHTS OF ACCESS, RECTIFICATION, ERASURE, AND RESTRICTION

You may inquire as to whether BrandYourself is Processing Personal Information about you, request access to Personal Information, and ask that we correct, amend or delete your Personal Information where it is inaccurate. Where otherwise permitted by applicable law, you may contact BrandYourself or BrandYourself.com, Inc., 53 West James Street, Suite 401, Lancaster, PA 17603, Attn: Privacy Policy or use any of the methods set out in this Privacy Policy to request access to, receive (port), seek rectification, or request erasure of Personal Information held about you by BrandYourself. Please include your full name, email address associated with your account, and a detailed description of your data request. Such requests will be processed in line with local laws.

Although BrandYourself makes good faith efforts to provide Individuals with access to their Personal Information, there may be circumstances in which BrandYourself is unable to provide access, including but not limited to: where the information contains legal privilege, would compromise others’ privacy or other legitimate rights, where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the Individual’s privacy in the case in question or where it is commercially proprietary. If BrandYourself determines that access should be restricted in any particular instance, we will provide you with an explanation of why that determination has been made and a contact point for any further inquiries. To protect your privacy, BrandYourself will take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to or making any changes to your Personal Information.

### 7\. DATA RETENTION

BrandYourself retains the Personal Information we receive as described in this Privacy Policy for as long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, pursue legitimate business purposes, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws. We will retain de-personalized information after your account has been closed. Your profile may continue to be displayed in the services of others (e.g., search engine results) until they refresh their cache. 

### 8\. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.

By using the Site or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Site. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Site or sending an e-mail to you. You may have a legal right to receive this notice in writing.

### 9\. INTERNATIONAL USERS

By using the Site, BrandYourself will transfer data to the United States. By choosing to visit the Site, utilize the Services or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of the state of Delaware in the United States of America, and the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with BrandYourself or the Site will be in accordance with the Terms.

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and to Processing of your data globally. By providing your Personal Information, you consent to any transfer and Processing in accordance with this Policy.

### 10\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The Services are not directed to children under 13 (and in certain jurisdictions under the age of 16) years of age, and BrandYourself does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13 (and in certain jurisdictions under the age of 16) years of age. If you are under the age of 18, you must have your parent’s permission to access the Services. BrandYourself urges parents to instruct their children never to give out their real names, addresses, or phone numbers, without parental permission, when online. If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, you may alert us at contact BrandYourself or BrandYourself.com, Inc., 53 West James Street, Suite 401, Lancaster, PA 17603, Attn: Privacy Policy. If we learn that we have collected any Personal Information from children under 13 (and in certain jurisdictions under the age of 16), we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account.

### 11\. REDRESS/COMPLIANCE AND ACCOUNTABILITY

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, this Privacy Policy, or how to lodge a complaint with the appropriate authority, please contact BrandYourself at contact BrandYourself or BrandYourself.com, Inc., 53 West James Street, Suite 401, Lancaster, PA 17603, Attn: Privacy Policy]. We will address your concerns and attempt to resolve any privacy issues in a timely manner. 

### 12\. OTHER RIGHTS AND IMPORTANT INFORMATION

### 12.1 CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. You understand and agree that you will be deemed to have accepted the updated Privacy Policy if you use the Services after the updated Privacy Policy is posted on the Services. If at any point you do not agree to any portion of the Privacy Policy then in effect, you must immediately stop using the Services.

  * **Revision to the Privacy Policy.** We may revise this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion, so review it periodically. If you continue to visit this Site and use the services made available to you after such changes have been made, you hereby provide your consent to the changes.

  * **Posting of Revised Privacy Policy.** If there are any material changes to this Privacy Policy, BrandYourself will notify you by email or as otherwise required by applicable law. We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective immediately when it is posted (or upon notice as applicable). If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically. 

### 12.2 CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the Third Parties to whom we have disclosed their Personal Information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of Personal Information disclosed to those parties. BrandYourself does not share Personal Information with Third Parties for their own marketing purposes.

### 13\. DEFINITIONS

The following capitalized terms shall have the meanings herein as set forth below.

  * “ **Agent** ” means any Third Party that Processes Personal Information pursuant to the instructions of, and solely for, BrandYourself or to which BrandYourself discloses Personal Information for use on its behalf.

  * “ **Personal Information** ” is any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“ **Individual”** ).

  * “ **Process** ” or “ **Processing** ” means any operation which is performed upon Personal Information, whether or not by automatic means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction.

  * “ **Third Party** ” is any company, natural or legal person, public authority, agency, or body other than the Individual, BrandYourself or BrandYourself’s Agents.

### 14\. REVISION HISTORY

  * Privacy Policy: Effective: [●]

  * Privacy Policy: Effective: 1/1/18

  * Privacy Policy: Effective: 6/4/18
